ipmart.in 2016-10-24

# Privacy Policy - by IPmart India

  * Your shopping cart is empty!

IPmart India considers your privacy to be of paramount importance. It makes sure every transaction follows the standard privacy policy. As such, IPmart India uses only customer's name and personal information as directed by the policy. We concentrate on collecting information that is relevant to our dealings with you. The collected information is retained with IPmart India for as long as required legally and as long as it is relevant for the purposes for which the data was collected. However, it has to be noted that the website allows free surfing and browsing of its content without you having to provide your personal details.

#### Contact Details

IPmart India collects customer information to process the order of a product. We use the collected data for your future purchases or claims from the website. The information that we collect includes your name, title, gender, delivery address, contact number, fax and payment details. Payment details include your card and bank account details.

#### Uses

It is only after you have furnished us with your details that we can accept the placing of your order, process its payment and deliver the content to you. It helps us to keep you updated about the status of your order if we have these details.

Providing the details allow IPmart India to identify you easily so that you can have access to sections of the website that might have been restricted to you earlier. Your personal details help us detect fraud or site abuses and credit risk reduction. We can provide you with quicker marketing or customer service assistance too. However, if we sell the whole or a part of the business, we may require to transfer our databases that have your personal information.

#### More Uses - Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

IPmart India would like to walk you through the other uses that we may use your information for. We may use it for opinion and market researches. When we use your information for such purposes, we will keep your details anonymous and use it for statistical purposes. 

IPmart India updates its customers by sending information regarding the company, its site, other websites, products, sales promotions, newsletters, and matters relating to IPmart India's business partners. You can unsubscribe to them if you are not interested in receiving these updates. We will process your request within 7 working days.

IPmart India uses personal data to ascertain location and usage of certain aspects of the site. The collected data may be passed on to third parties. The data will be anonymized and as such you will not be identified personally.

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account. We use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and interests.

#### Modification/Alteration to Privacy Policy

We may modify, change or alter any part of this privacy policy at any given point of time. The revised privacy policy will be effective immediately after being posted on the website. Hence, it is the sole responsibility of each and every user to review the privacy policy of the website carefully to know of any revisions made to it.

#### Demographic and Profile Data

Personal information is used to:

Provide the services you request;

Resolve disputes & solve issues.

Understand, measure & analyse consumer interest in the products;

Provide information on product offers & updates;

Promote a genuine service;

Occasionally request participation in online survey.

**Note:** You can send your product to the address stated below:

#### Personal Information:

Personal information may be shared with our other business units to:

Prevent or detect identity theft, fraud and other illegal operations;

Correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services;

Cater to a legally-compliant request made by a third party. We will not rent, trade or share your identifiable PII, like name and address, with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent

Facilitate joint or co-branded services that may be requested by you where such services are provided by more than one business unit. Should such a transaction occur, the other business entity (or the newly annexed entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy to use your personal information

Identify your IP address that will help diagnose problems in our server and to manage our website. The identification also helps to recognise you and gather broad demographic information

To determine your requirements. Cookies and other technologies, such as pixel tags and clear gifs, may be used to store certain types of information each time you visit our website. This enables us to determine what your requirements are and promote advertisements accordingly. You may choose to disable cookies. 

For promotional materials. As we use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the internet, they may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services to target advertisements for goods and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.

#### Third Party

However, it has to be noted that there are cases where we require sending across your personal details to the franchisor. It is after your approval that the franchisor can use the information to sell products to you either directly or indirectly to carry out transactions with you. Secondly, we may also send across your details to a third party, for example, courier or delivery agency so they can deliver the product to your address.

It is however to be noted that we do not rent or sell your personal details to anyone nor do we allow anyone to use your details for their marketing interests. We use your personal information in a way that is described by the privacy policy.

Apart from the above mentioned third parties, we may also share your details to other companies which are in the same group, like agents and sub-contractors, to help IPmart India with the various uses of your details in our data set. We do not encourage the exchange of personal details that do not adhere to the laws of the privacy policy. If we are required to share your personal details to third parties, we do it only after your consent. Note that the website may contain links related to third parties or other sites. IPmart India is not responsible for any of the privacy policy of these other sites.

We take measures to keep your details safe and secure. We also have the third parties follow our privacy policy. 

#### Expectations from You:

IPmart India assures the protection of your private information. However, it is expected that as a customer you furnish accurate details only and keep us updated about any changes.

####   

#### Tracking

You can track the details of your transactions by logging onto the website with your details. You can view orders that are complete, open and those that are to be dispatched. You are expected to keep your details unavailable to unauthorized third parties. We accept liability of passwords if it is our fault.  
Please furnish your personal details only if you accept the terms and conditions made available here.

####   

#### Fraud Prevention

IPmart India takes the required measures to curb any fraudulent activities. We have teamed up with standard and authorized agencies that are well endowed with credit card policies and fraud prevention methods.

####   

#### Cookies

Cookies, as you may be aware of, are minuscule text files which help IPmart India server to identify your computer when you visit pages on our website. Cookies help recognize your internet protocol (IP) address.  
You may restrict the use of your cookies. However, this would only affect your usability of your website. You may not be able to visit certain pages if you do not enable the cookies. IPmart India uses cookies only to enhance your experience. IPmart India cookies do not contain personal details and they are free of viruses.  
Cookies are used to recognize the internet browser. The data that is collected is used with the authorization of the user to identify visitors to IPmart India website.

####   

#### Security

IPmart India transactions are secured by technologies like Firewall and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). All the transactions are held by secure servers. To keep your transactions secure you should be careful about sending your details in unencrypted electronic communications with Zoffio. We may, as a measure to secure your financial details and transactions, require you to provide proof of identity before disclosing information to you. You are completely responsible to keep your password secure and safe.

####   

#### Copyright

IPmart India has complete copyright over the Privacy Policy discussed. Violation of the copyright is not allowed by any party. The violation of IPmart India copyright will be subject to legal action.
